(Lee Je Hoon)
(Jang Hyuk Jin, Bae Yoo Ram, Kim Eui Sung, Pyo Ye Jin)
(Taxi Driver 3)
(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Children and animals were filmed under guidelines.)
All right. One million dollars in capital.
You managed to squirrel that away.
I swore I'd make a comeback with this no matter what,
- and that's what got me through. - What business were you planning?
Let's go with a site.
(Site: Illegal Gambling Sites)
That's not enough money.
What are you talking about? I did tech for two years.
(Tech: A scam using stocks or crypto bait)
And I did ping for almost two years.
It's time I moved up to a site. Right?
Gosh, he's going to be so disappointed.
Why don't you lay it out for him?
For ping, you just set up computers in an office and that's it,
but a site is like building a broadcast station.
You need at least three locations for the casino and call center.
That alone will cost you 150,000 dollars a month.
What, 150,000 dollars a month?
- Seriously? Why is it so expensive? - And that's the rock-bottom price.
The closer you are to the city, the more expensive it'll be.
And that's not including protection and broker fees for the cops.
Then there are the accounts.
A site gets 200 to 300 cases a day,
so you need burner accounts from "Jang,"
- a mule account opening company. - Doesn't this sound like...
some kind of business seminar?
By setting up a corporation under a Payment Gateway...
She sounds so professional, I find myself starting to trust her.
- I know, right? Gosh. - Goodness.
What's the point? It's all illegal.
- Right. - Right.
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
What's this? It says it costs 25,000 dollars a month?
And that doesn't include marketing and franchising fees.
Darn it, why is so much stuff not included?
Even if we set it up for you for next to nothing,
you couldn't run it for two months with what you have now.
But if you insist on going for a site,
you could run a rinky-dink site, maybe?
- All right, now. - Goodness.
She's the best in Asia when it comes to making these sites.
Right? Even if it's a bit of a hassle,
let's stick with ping a bit longer for two years, save up,
and then we can move on to a site.
I think that's the better move.
If you're the one saying it, Writer Go,
I guess that's the right move.
And here.
What's this?
A little something to celebrate you getting out.
(Payment Gateway: Setup and maintenance fees)
This is a premium database.
The success rate...
should be over 80 percent.
Gosh, you really shouldn't have.
You're the only one...
who always looks out for me, Writer Go.
Okay, fine! We'll go with ping!
You've always got to listen to the experts.
- It always pays off in the end. - Don't you worry.
Hey, you two, come on up and get your consultation.
So, it's our turn now?
All right, young fellas.
Why don't you show me how much money you've brought?
We'll pay you afterward.
You little jerks!
Hey, I thought you said you had the money!
This is...
What is this? Hey! If you pull a stunt like this on me,
you make me look like an idiot for vouching for you!
Hey, we're not trying to stiff you. We'll pay you with our earnings.
That makes more sense, doesn't it?
These guys...
Why are you covering that up? You have to set us up too.
I thought you said you don't have any money.
We're not running a charity here.
You want me to put you in the ground?
You've got a way with words.
How about we go outside and expose what you're doing here?
We could make easy-to-digest Shorts and flood the algorithm.
Do you want that?
Do you?
You mentioned virtual accounts and whatnot.
I know how it works. I've done it. Those corporate accounts,
you just find a defunct company that isn't officially dissolved.
If you set up affiliate accounts, you can churn them out.
Or post on Jang's telegram,
and you'd get takers in a day or two.
Plenty of kids will DM you their IDs for a fake loan consult.
All right. I've heard enough from you geniuses.
We're going to discuss it among ourselves,
so why don't you two step outside...
and have yourselves a nice smoke.
Now that's more like it.
Let's just keep things friendly.
We're not amateurs, you know?
Just set us up with whatever makes the most money.
Those darn little thugs.
It's like they grew up on Shorts.
Writer Go, I'm so sorry.
I'll go talk some sense into them. All right?
Hey!
See? I told you. Those jerks are cowards.
Totally. You see that?
What is this?
Gosh, check out the death stare on this farmer.
Who's this?
I'm sorry.
Writer Go! My gosh, Writer Go!
Writer Go!
Writer Go! What happened?
Writer Go. I just made the introduction.
- Please, Writer Go, I... - What are you talking about?
What?
You're one of our best clients, Mr. Lee.
- Aren't you? - Right.
Why don't you go and relax?
As soon as we're set up again,
I'll come and get you myself.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you so much.
Clean this up.
- Hallelujah! - Hallelujah!
(7 years ago)
Four hundred years!
For 400 years, in the land of Egypt,
the people of Israel lived in bondage.
But just as God led them to a land of milk and honey,
- the land of Canaan! - Amen!
- Amen! - So too has He, our Shepherd,
spoken to us.
God speaks.
Lord.
"Leave this shabby, worn-out building..."
"for a comfortable and magnificent new sanctuary!"
"Lead my lambs to it!"
- For so He has commanded! - Hallelujah!
- Hallelujah! - Hallelujah!
Hallelujah!
(Welcome in the Lord's love)
But...
are you sure we can do it for that cheap?
Are you sure you won't lose money, Pastor?
In Pennsylvania, where they drafted the Declaration of Independence,
my brother in faith, Cheol Min, and I did a very similar project.
To build a sanctuary for less than half the going rate,
that's a loss financially.
But when I think of the joy it will bring you elders...
and all the members of this spirit-filled congregation,
that's a profit you can't measure in dollars.
That's a true blessing.
Amen.
Indeed.
Thank you.
We're grateful for meeting a pastor who's also a brilliant architect...
After I get back from the US, I'll come and see you all again.
(First Heaven Church)
- Stop! - Wait a minute, hold on!
- We're prosecutors. - Prosecutors? Why?
We have a warrant for your arrest.
Arrest? What arrest? Darn it! Hey! Let go of me!
- Hey! What division are you from? - Move out of the way!
Let go of me.
Let me go! Hey, let go!
Get your hands off me! Let go!
Pleasure to meet you. You're Ju Seok Bong?
You've got quite the personality.
Oh, gosh.
It's all over now, okay?
Have a seat.
Excuse me, Prosecutor.
Here.
(First Heaven Church)
Oh, dear.
What are you going to do now?
I bet you already paid to be smuggled out of the country.
That's life,
Prosecutor.
Article 347 of the Criminal Code, fraud.
With your priors, Article 351, aggravated penalty for repeaters.
You worked as a team, so Article 30, joint principal offenders.
The damages per victim exceed 500,000 dollars,
we'll also tack on Article three of the Specific Economic Crimes Act.
At a minimum, you're looking at seven years.
That mole...
You've got to be kidding me. What is this? How pathetic.
Tell you what. For a man like you, Ju Seok Bong,
there are two options.
Options?
Option 1. You go to prison and pay for your sins for 10 years.
Option two.
You take on a much more comfortable line of work...
and enjoy a life of complete freedom.
If I could actually choose the second one...
And legally, at that.
What's the catch?
You just have to join my company as a founding member.
So,
will you join us?
Hold on a second, Prosecutor.
I know this great guy. Cheol Min!
Get over here and say hello.
Hello, sir.
Works for me.
(Interrogation room)
You guys haven't eaten yet, have you?
Here.
Go and eat comfortably.
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you, sir.
Hello.
I know the investigation must have been rough,
so I'll get straight to the point.
The Apgujeong hustler.
I'll give you credit, you've got real talent.
With that talent,
you handled the hacking and website, the whole works.
If this goes to trial, you're probably looking at 15 years.
- What am I supposed to do? - What do you think?
My life is over.
It's not over yet.
At the startup I'm putting together,
you can keep doing exactly what you're doing now.
If you're interested, of course.
No risk of getting caught out of the blue like this.
A secure startup.
And this is a gift for our founding members.
What do you say?
I get the feeling this company isn't exactly legit.
Why would a prosecutor like you do this?
Let's say I'm tired of doing good and want to have some fun.
Being a prosecutor is boring, isn't it?
What's the point of working so hard to lock guys up for so little pay?
They get out in a few years and end up owning entire buildings.
So I'm planning on quitting.
And instead of a severance package,
someone as charming and talented as you...
would be the perfect person to scout.
I'm in.
Gosh, this is killer!
So this is our new office?
But why is no one else here?
After a few counter-spy ops here, everyone just left on their own.
It's a little too empty for my taste.
Then we can just hire our own people to fill the spots.
Let's fill it with foreigners. Undocumented ones.
It'll make things easier.
Then I guess we'll need our own police substation.
- Good idea, Officer Kim. - And you, Prosecutor?
Me?
I'll just be traveling around the island,
taking some landscape photos.
And speaking of which,
why don't we take a picture?
To commemorate our new venture.
- Writer Go, is it good? - Just a little...
A little... Okay, that's good.
We're taking a photo! Get over here, quick!
- We're losing the light! Come on. - Okay.
- Hurry. - Get in here!
Okay.
Come on, smile like Ju Seok Bong, will you?
- Okay. - The man of the hour. All right.
(Taxi Driver 3)
Just like Driver Kim said, Writer Go was...
a prosecutor in the Special Investigations Division.
This guy, Officer Kim, is a corrupt cop with a long record.
And the female motel owner... My gosh.
She has an illegal gambling record...
and was a programmer for the top illegal gaming site.
Then there's Seo Hwang, a con artist with ten priors.
And this jerk, Boss Choi, is a former overseas mercenary.
He was investigated for contract killing...
and illegal weapons possession.
And...
every single one of these jerks...
has one thing in common. Their charges were dropped.
I'm not surprised.
Writer Go must've dropped their charges while he was a prosecutor.
So he handpicked his own crew before he quit.
Since we've found their base, let's just go in and wipe them out.
We can't yet.
Why not? What's the problem?
If we just get rid of them right now,
we won't be able to do anything about...
all their criminal franchises overseas.
But we don't even know where those overseas franchises are.
How are we supposed to track them all down?
Writer Go creates crime scenarios...
and distributes them to all the franchises.
That means this island is connected to a global criminal network.
But to handle that kind of volume, they'd need a dedicated server.
And that server...
is most likely hidden somewhere around here.
- Hey. - Gosh! You scared me!
It's just me. Reporter Bong.
Do you have to sneak up on us like that?
Can't you just show up normally? Like you're clocking in for work.
Sorry, force of habit.
There we go.
But squatting for so long, doesn't it hurt your knees?
I'm fine.
I'm okay because I have this. It's good for your joints.
- Gosh, this is... - Hey, isn't that from...
It looks familiar.
- So, what did you need? - Right.
I overheard you guys talking.
I thought maybe this could help.
Okay, guys.
Let's move it there.
Go on.
Those are servers and cooling equipment.
To bypass a dedicated server, I'll need my own equipment.
It's back at the office.
- I'll go get it in the morning. - Okay.
Driver Kim, can you hold out until then?
Go on. I'll find a way to stall them.
How? Those jerks will kill anyone on a whim.
So what?
We'll just do some killing of our own.
Hey, killing them sounds good.
- Who should we kill first? - Who first? We're killing them all.
- Let's go all out. - Right.
So, what's the order? We kill this one, then that one?
- Yes, that works. - Can I be next?
Oh, no. Let's just go by age.
- Oh, so I guess I'm up first. - Yes.
- Who's up after me? - That'd be me. Let's do that.
- We're going to get rich off this. - Yes.
The presentation is over,
but I still don't see any money on the table.
As I mentioned, our guy went to get the money.
Right.
I saw him leave on the boat.
Why don't you start deciding which business you'd like to open?
So what you're suggesting, Writer Go,
is we start with ping for two years to learn the ropes and get set up,
then switch to the site model? Is that it?
That's right.
I'll continue to send you scripts for new profitable plans quarterly.
And one more thing.
Since it got a little messy earlier, I'll take ten percent off...
your monthly subscription fee.
This is hilarious.
It's like a chicken franchise where you pay royalties to corporate...
- and sends you their secret sauce. - You're right.
It's pretty similar.
So, to ensure your future business is successful,
we'll do our best to help.
All right then, we will...
trust the expert...
- and go with ping. - Wait a minute!
No, wait. We have the manpower,
and if we just push a little harder, can't we go right to the site?
And from the pitch, it sounds like the cost difference isn't huge.
Sir, instead of doing too much from the start,
- build a solid base first, then... - Come on.
Come on. "A solid base"?
For us, if you get caught, it's over.
- Then let's go all in. Right? - Exactly.
It's about building a solid base, but we also need to save capital,
so we can upgrade the site later. I've explained all this already,
so why act like this is new to you? What do you want from me?
No.
I say we go straight for the site. I don't have much time left.
I can't afford to waste time like this.
You all came here because I said so, didn't you? Right?
- So just do what I say. - Says who? It's my money!
Then why not split the capital and do both at the same time?
If we do both, at least one is bound to succeed.
Don't be ridiculous!
You're new, so just stay out of it.
Stay out of it? I can't believe this guy.
Old man, just because I'm quiet, do you think I'm a pushover?
Did you just call me an old man?
With that ridiculous hair, you're getting an attitude with me?
Hey!
You'll startle the Buddha.
You people have no respect.
Monk.
I think we'll need a moment to talk amongst ourselves.
Right.
I just finished setting up the barbecue.
Guess I'll have to feed it to the dogs.
Darn these guys.
I was wondering what that smell was. So it was the barbecue.
Perfect, I was starving anyway.
Since the fire's already going, let's eat first and talk later.
We're all in this together, right? Yes, let's go.
You got an extra pair of gloves? I'm a master at the grill.
- I love meat! Meat! - Gosh, my hip is killing me.
- Here, eat up. - Here, honey.
Having a barbecue at a temple.
- You too. - Gosh, it's delicious.
It's really good.
To think they were mortal enemies just a while ago.
Call me when the job comes up.
Aren't you having any?
- I'm fine. Please eat up. - This meat is incredible.
By the way,
there's something to take care of before we start the business.
The taxi company CEO who came with me...
I want him taken care of.
- Pardon? - You saw what happened earlier.
He's not the boss, but he acts like it and expects special treatment.
It's really getting on my nerves.
I did all the research and put this whole plan together.
All he needs to do is put his money in and take his cut.
But he still thinks he's the boss. That jerk.
So you're asking me to...
That guy... Boss Choi?
He seemed terrifyingly good at his job.
I'll make it worth his while,
so let's get him on it.
Gosh, this Maitreya Buddha looks ancient.
It looks like it's over 500 years old.
I doubt you wanted to know the Buddha's age...
when you asked to speak with me in private.
What was it you urgently needed to discuss?
Since you put it that way,
I'll get straight to the point.
I've been holding my tongue for a long time,
but I just can't take it anymore.
I'm older than him,
it's my money, and I'm the CEO,
but from the way he acts, you'd think he was the boss.
When all he did was drive us here.
Here's what I'm getting at, Monk.
I need you to take care of that taxi driver who came with me.
I'll make sure you're handsomely rewarded.
What's this all of a sudden?
I mean, once the tour is over,
isn't it only natural for the guide to disappear?
Right?
That's it.
His face...
- Blessed be the Goddess of Mercy. - His face...
Can I have a word with you?
After listening, I realized we don't need this many people.
The money comes to me first.
Except for me,
can't you kill everyone else?
It's easier to deal with one person than a group,
and it'll make getting the job done smoother, right?
I'll even pay you extra.
Even Kim Do Gi?
- Yes. - I thought you two were a thing.
What a nice day.
Finally.
Fi...
Finally?
Throw that jerk into the ocean.
Drop him somewhere deep,
so no one will ever find him.
Does that make me a bad person?
What...
What are you saying?
Make sure you kill him.
Honey.
- Honey. - Honey!
Honey, I brought your favorite meat.
- This is just... - I think it's spoiled.
A complete madhouse.
Driver Kim, in your opinion,
who do you think they'll listen to out of all of us?
I wonder.
They'll likely listen to me, right? I'm the boss, after all.
I have a feeling they'll listen to Driver Kim.
He and Writer Go seemed to be on the same page.
I have a feeling they'll listen to Go Eun.
It's easier to deal with one person, right?
What's their deal? Those losers.
It doesn't look like they even want to hire us.
Then what's with them asking us to kill each other?
If they don't intend on hiring us, why did they come out here?
I'm not curious enough to...
finding that out.
Go Eun told them to kill all of us!
What if those guys...
decide to listen to her right this second?
Shouldn't we be coming up with a plan right now?
How long have we been on this island?
About six or seven years?
It's about time we moved.
Let's start packing our things.
This time, let's find somewhere with a little more charm...
and a nice atmosphere.
Are the workers coming with us or are we hiring new ones?
We'll be traveling as light as possible.
Right.
Writer Go.
Since we're moving anyway,
why don't we set up near a church? I think I'm...
Amitabha Buddha
I'm more cut out to be a pastor.
Knock yourself out.
What about renewing Lee Gi Hyeon's contract?
- We already took all his money. - I sent my men to take care of him.
That's why we get paid upfront, isn't it?
Right. What about the people from the taxi company?
Once they bring the money,
we'll take care of them right away.
(Samheung Inn)
There are too many eyes on us here,
let's meet at Reporter Bong's shack later.
I have to check on something first.
Okay.
Yes?
The boat should be arriving any minute now,
so let's get the meeting started.
The sooner we get this over with, the better.
I was waiting. And it sounds like the boat's arriving right on time.
I'll see you shortly.
- I think Go Eun was right. - What are you talking about?
Lee Gi Hyeon is dead.
What? They took the money and just killed him?
As soon as Chief Park gets back, I think they'll get rid of us too.
How much time do you think you need?
Even if I find the server room on the first try,
if they have multi-layered security, it'll be at least 30 to 40 minutes.
- Thirty to forty minutes. - And that's if I'm lucky.
And one more thing.
Samheung Temple has to be empty.
Driver Kim, what are you doing?
How does it look?
- Doesn't it look like a cash bag? - Wait.
- Give me a hand with this. - Sure.
Yes, Writer Go.
The thing is,
I was hoping we could talk, just us, before the main meeting.
Right.
Okay, I'll head over there right now.
What's going on? You can't leave without telling me the plan.
There is no plan. Until Go Eun finishes her work,
we all just have to stall for time as best we can.
Hey...
What?
Hey, Monk. It's me.
I was hoping we could talk privately before the meeting.
Somewhere private.
Okay, let's meet at the gukbap place right now.
Gosh, if everyone just takes off, what am I supposed to do?
Gosh, how am I supposed to stall for time? Goodness.
Okay, let's do this.
The boat's already here,
so why were you in such a hurry to see me?
Get in. We can talk on the way.
It's the bag, isn't it?
Goodness. Come on, get in.
I'll put it in the back for you.
Gosh.
All right, then.
I'll ensure a safe ride.
Gosh, the gukbap is here. Thank you so much.
Here, let me get that.
- Is your name A Na? - Yes. And you are?
I'm Jang Seong Cheol.
I'll go on up and get things ready for the meeting.
(Samheung Gukbap)
This is a very serious matter.
Is there a problem?
Take a look. This here...
This is a Busan pork and rice soup, with boiled pork.
You see the clear broth?
But look, there are sesame seeds in it.
And sesame seeds are a hallmark of the Naju style, are they not?
I have to say, it's quite a perplexing combination.
I see. You must have one of those food blogs.
- A blog? No, certainly not. - Perhaps it's time...
you get to the point.
What was it you needed to discuss so urgently?
- Monk. - Yes.
Either way, I have the money.
There's no need to rush.
What I wanted to say was...
Wait, what's this?
Not wheat noodles,
but buckwheat noodles?
This is the Gangwon Province style.
Is A Na from Gangneung?
Is her family from Gangneung?
Is she?
Ma'am!
Hey, we've got plenty of time left.
Let's kill some time, just us. I heard that back in Apgujeong...
I need to go there and get ready.
All the money's here anyway. What's the rush?
Man, I even got the small bills. This thing weighs a ton.
This should be enough for the pot, right?
Not that it matters, since I'm going to win it all anyway.
- Isn't that company money? - So? I'll win and put it back.
So what should we play? Go-Stop?
What are you going to do if you lose it all?
If you lose, are you going to bet an arm or something?
Why is this thing still attached?
I can't even hold a woman's hand. Might as well cut it off.
- Seotda. How about it? - Seotda? Okay!
Am I in the wrong place?
So, when are you going to bring it up?
That urgent matter you wanted to discuss.
Right.
You still haven't decided on my proposal, have you?
Right, not yet.
Actually, I had a few drinks with the CEO,
and we had a real heart-to-heart.
I think we can spare him.
Seriously? You called me here in such a rush just for that?
Hey, what could be more urgent than this?
All right, fine.
Let's go back up. Looks like you brought the money anyway.
Then kill the accountant instead.
I've decided she has to die.
She's getting prettier every day. I can't have that.
She'll definitely cheat on me.
You're a real handful, you know that?
A handful?
This is good to have when you're tired.
Want some?
It's really delicious.
Delicious.
Well?
Look at these jerks.
Gosh, how many layers of security did they put up?
So paranoid.
Gap, Oh.
(Gap, Oh: March, June)
Hey, it's Dok, Sa.
(Dok, Sa: January, April)
Al, Li.
(Al, Li: January, February)
That must sting. I'll make you all some spicy soup later.
You're pretty good.
Man, Seotda looks easy, but it's actually pretty tough.
- Hey, what gives? - It's time to get to work.
Hey, you can't just win and run. That's just bad form.
If you really have to go, good form means you leave the money.
Why would I leave my own money?
Because it was my money to begin with.
Hey, we haven't even gotten a call. They'll call if they need us.
Come on.
At least clean us out before you leave.
Then we'll call it fair.
Fine. Let's all go all-in for the final round.
I'm in.
Okay, last hand's over and we're starting a new game,
so I'll be the one to deal, right?
- Deal. - All right.
Abracadabra.
(Firewall bypass 1: Failed)
(Firewall bypass 2: Failed)
(3rd failure triggers server shutdown.)
(Firewall bypass successful)
And as a little bonus, the premium database.
Go!
Honey. It's me. Where are you?
Hey, honey. I'm driving right now.
- Are you done with work? - Yes.
- I miss you so much. - You do?
Oh, my gosh, that's crazy.
I was just thinking I missed you too.
We're totally on the same wavelength.
- Then come see me. You will, right? - Of course I will.
Honey, I'm coming as soon as I can. Just wait for me.
Okay.
- I love you, honey. - I love you more!
Darn it. Seriously.
Get out.
- What? - You heard her. She misses me.
You're telling me to get out? Here?
We can finish our conversation after I get back.
Finish what?
What is there to finish?
We've been driving around until sunset.
We haven't said a single word to each other!
What? Do you want to see my girlfriend too?
Unbelievable...
Go.
(Deluxe Taxi)
That jerk! Who's he dealing with? Does he have any idea who I am?
Where am I?
In Andong, there's Jungang Market. It used to be an old cattle market.
In the market's center, they add scallions, oxblood, cabbage,
and simmer them into this rich, hearty stew.
The gukbap there is amazing. The line is always incredibly long.
But this gukbap...
is made with a rich, slow-brewed beef bone broth.
But speaking of bone broth, try the Uiryeong bean sprout gukbap.
- That stuff is on another level. - Excuse me a moment, Mr. Jang.
Forgive me for saying this,
but I have walking and bowel issues, and intermittent claudication.
I suffer from spinal stenosis that can cause these issues.
I can't sit still for long. So, could you stop talking about soup,
and get to the point?
What? Monk, I thought you liked gukbap.
Based on your face, you look like a total soup fanatic.
This information is highly prized among soup connoisseurs, Monk.
Your knack for reading faces has really gotten rusty.
So please, just get to the point. My back is really starting to hurt.
And now my ears are starting to hurt too.
So please, just get on with it.
(An Go Eun: Done)
Yes, my apologies.
- The thing is... - Yes.
Since I'll probably be asking you for many favors in the future, Monk,
I prepared a small gift of my appreciation.
A gift?
Yes.
Ta-da!
It's roasted seaweed. The delicious kind.
Here, look.
You see this seaweed? You just tear it open like this.
See?
Wrap it around a bite of rice like this,
and then you eat it.
It's not too salty, and it's so savory.
It's got a clean taste. Absolutely amazing.
Gosh, is that it?
You came all this way just to give me seaweed?
And not even a whole box, just a single pack.
If you don't want the seaweed, I guess I'll just have it myself.
Anyway, I'll get to my point in due time.
Is he trying to make me curse?
Gosh. They say you're supposed to talk less as you get older.
But that jerk...
Where did that jerk go?
You can run all you want, but you can't escape Buddha's hand.
(An Go Eun: Done)
Alright, all in!
All in.
- Jjangttaeng. - Gosh!
- To beat a Jjangttaeng... - It's a Gwangttaeng.
Oh dear, what are you going to do now you've lost the company's money?
Oh, no. All I have is a nine.
It's a Gwangttaeng!
Yes, I won! Game over.
Man, that was the best hand I could get.
Here, take a taxi home. It's not safe to walk.
That was fun.
- Just thinking of it upsets me. - Why?
- Weren't you up there? - Don't even get me started.
That guy, the taxi company's CEO, asked to meet, so I went.
And gosh, he just went on and on about some stupid gukbap.
I'm telling you, I thought my ears were going to bleed.
Darn it...
Weird, right?
I'm telling you, let's just get rid of them all!
What are you doing here?
The guys from the taxi company wouldn't let me leave.
(Successfully received Premium DB)
(I'll put it to good use! Thanks, Premium DB!)
By any chance,
- did we send them the script? - What script are you talking about?
The boat's already here,
so why were you in such a hurry to see me?
Get in. We can talk on the way.
Hey, honey.
Are you done with work?
Yes.
Darn it!
Kim Do Gi... Kim Do Gi, you scum!
- Darn it! - Darn.
What is this? All this grass...
No. What is this? Please... This can't be happening!
A Na!
Ana! Are you okay?
Darn it.
What's all the commotion? Did something happen?
- Hey. What's that smoke? - Isn't that the Police Substation?
Oh, no! Wait, hold on...
My gosh!
Hey!
Your opponent...
isn't over there, is he?
"Do no harm." Do not take a life.
How can you defy Buddha's teachings like that?
- You okay? - Let's go.
Darn it.
(Server down)
What's that? Who did that?
- It wasn't me. - Me neither.
It was me.
A Na!
(Police Station)
I took care of everything.
I wasn't sure what else I could do to help.
- Nice work. - You're the best.
(Deluxe Taxi)
What happened with their affiliates?
They should be pretty much taken care of by now.
I sent it as a "special DB." They'll probably open it, right?
Let's get out of here on the boat before those guys notice.
- Okay. - I think they've already caught on.
You really got me good.
It feels good getting a compliment from a former prosecutor.
You guys doing all this...
What exactly is in it for you?
I've been racking my brain, but I just don't get it.
Why would you go to such lengths?
Why?
Why go through all this? Why?
I'm asking you, why are you doing all this?
Because I care about them.
The new mom who's trying to save even a little on baby supplies,
who spends all day looking through resale apps.
The eight-year-old buying gloves for her father in the hospital...
by breaking the piggy bank she'd been saving up for a year.
And that man who only feels secure when he has 5,000 dollars.
I care about them a lot.
Now I see.
Why people always died or disappeared in your wake.
But what are you going to do?
This time,
that's going to be you.
Darn it.
Darn.
(Samheung Inn)
I think that siren's for us.
- Come on, to the docks! Quick! - Right.
(Deluxe Taxi)
Darn it.
Closer!
(Deluxe Taxi)
- Darn it. - Gosh.
Follow them this way.
I'll lure those guys away. Secure the boat while I do.
Okay, I'll go on ahead and get the engine started.
Hurry back.
Die!
(Deluxe Taxi)
Those jerks. They think they can mess with Samheung Island?
What are you doing? Get after them!
It's bulletproof glass!
Hey, go!
Bulletproof glass? Who are these guys?
You underestimated Samheung Island!
- You can't escape this island. - Floor it!
(Deluxe Taxi)
There they are.
Ram them.
- Unbelievable. Seriously. - Let's run them down!
(Deluxe Taxi)
Kill them! Run them off the road!
Ram them!
Floor it!
Push them!
Come on!
(Deluxe Taxi)
- What? We're losing ground! - Hey, die!
Just ram them all off the road! Harder!
Floor it!
(Deluxe Taxi)
Step on it more!
Back off!
Run them off the road. Kill them.
That's it.
Die, Kim Do Gi, you jerk! Die!
- Step on it! - Back off!
Die!
Wait a second.
Why did I build another one of these? Go Eun will kill me.
But you must have one of these.
You never know what might happen.
(Deluxe Taxi)
If they never have to use it, all the better.
I should give Driver Kim a heads-up about it.
(EMP)
Driver Kim.
Oh, gosh.
Do Gi!
Driver Kim!
Are you hurt?
Yes, I'm fine.
What was all that?
Could it be...
What's with all these cars?
The high-power discharge takes all the electrical power...
and releases it all at once.
I guess that's what fried all the other cars.
The Deluxe Taxi is totaled.
What did you say?
- Chief Park, what did you do? - Well...
What? You did something...
that turned our taxi into junk just like that? Is that right?
- No, it's just that... - But thanks to him,
I'm still alive.
Thank you,
Chief Park.
Really?
In that case...
Great job, Chief Park.
In that case, great job. Good work, Jin Eon.
Don't you have a mind of your own?
What does my opinion matter? What matters is what Go Eun thinks.
What?
Looks like that boat over there is moving.
It's Writer Go.
Hey. You think you've won, don't you?
Think again.
All I need is me.
As long as I'm around, I can rebuild everything.
(Public Official ID Card, Supreme Prosecutors' Office)
Hello, this is Reporter Bong.
(NEWSTART, Live)
I've been away on assignment.
He's like a totally different person.
A ring providing goods and services for criminal acts,
earning massive profits in the process,
has finally been taken down.
This organization, centered around a former prosecutor,
spawned over a hundred overseas criminal franchises.
While the major media ignored this and remained silent,
our team has been covering this case.
We, the late Shin Kyung Soo investigative journalism team,
have witnessed firsthand...
what kind of lawless wasteland is created...
when a guardian of the law turns their back...
and abuses the very system they swore to protect.
You've all been through so much.
Tonight, premium Korean beef is on me.
Finally!
In that case, I'm definitely eating a lot tonight.
- Okay, let's go to the BBQ place. - Sounds good.
Wait, we still have to take care of business.
Take care of what business?
We have to end our operation before we can go eat. Right, Driver Kim?
- Like this? - You have to do it by the book.
But this isn't the Deluxe Taxi, so there's no radio...
Vehicle 5283 is now ending service.
- Time for some beef! - Let's go!
(Deluxe Taxi)
(We would like to thank Kim Sung Kyu and Lee Kyoung Young.)
(Deluxe Taxi 3)
Captain Kim Do Gi. How have you been?
Gosh, why is his phone off?
To just abandon his taxi, something serious must've happened.
It says Sergeant Yoo Seon Ah went AWOL during training.
She was killed in an explosion while trying to escape.
It's a military base. I'm sure of it.
He's getting closer to the Demarcation Line. This is unnerving.
Something's definitely happened to Driver Kim.
We have to get to Driver Kim right now.
Halt. Driver, step out of the vehicle.
- Identify yourself. - Captain Kim Do Gi.